So friends, ICICI Ptial has disclosed its quarter
to quarter 3 numbers.
So let's see what the
data is in the numbers for Quarter 3 in lakhs.
I'm telling you in the cross.
So see, in the last quarter the company had
generated revenue of Rs 1215 crore.   If we
talk about last year, 4516 crores, now
look at it, you will see 22302 crores going away.
So if you look at the total income of the company, you will
see it increasing year after year and quarter after quarter.  If we look at the net premium income of the company, then
in the last quarter it generated Rs 11843 crore and last
year it was Rs 12,261 crore, whereas now if you look at it,
you will see Rs 11809 crore going away. If you
look at the net premium i.e. net premium income, then
you will see it falling quarter after quarter year after year.  The
total income of the company has
increased because the revenue generated by the
company through investments was
seen to be much higher in this quarter.
Last quarter last year the company had incurred
losses through investments.
But a good amount of revenue has been generated in this quarter,
around Rs 10,745 crore.
Due to which the total income of the company is
seen increasing.  But
mostly these two things are not there.  The most
important thing is the company's APE, that is, its
annual premium income, which is
basically the most important.
So if we talk about that, the
APE of the company last year was
around Rs 2398 crore.  If we talk about the last quarter, it was
around Rs 2322 crore in the last quarter.  Whereas if you look at it now,
you can see that the API of the company is going away by about Rs 2436 crore.
So one
good thing that is coming out is that if you
look at the most important data here,
you will
see it increasing year after year and quarter after quarter.  Let us see
what the expenses of the company are. Basically, let me
tell you how much the company has shown. The profit
of the company in this quarter is
around Rs 2436 crore, whereas the market
estimate was also around Rs 2460 crore.
So look here, it is a little less
but you can see almost the same.  Let's
talk about expenses,
see the expenses of the company in the last quarter
were around 10100 sorry 11530 crores,
last year it was 497 crores, whereas if you look at it now,
you have seen 2233 crores going away.  In
such a situation, let us look at the net profit of the company.
So see, in the last quarter the
company was in profit of Rs 295 crore.  Last
year it was around Rs 324 crore, whereas if you look at it now,
you saw Rs 387 crore going away.
So if you look at the net profit, it is
seen increasing year after year and quarter after quarter.   We
can almost say that there is a jump of around 19 to 20% in the
company's profit year after
year, so the company's profits are looking good.  It is
seen increasing year by year and quarter by quarter.  And let's
talk about the NPA of the company and if we
look at the EPS here, it was ₹2.7 in the last quarter,
₹2.25 last year, if you look at it now, you can see it going to ₹2.70.
So if
seen overall, the number is not something special.
You can call it an average number because
basically, you got to see it around the market's estimate
regarding the company's AP APE i.e. annual
premium income, so
you got to
see the APE almost in line, there
is nothing special,
you did not get to see a big change year after year
because you got
to see a little bit of growth year after year, there is a
jump of around 2%, so
you got to see average type numbers, let's see
how the market reacts to this, if you liked the video then
please like it and also subscribe to the channel, thank you
and